let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "George Gervin’s 'most points scored in a quarter’ record was broken in 2015, by this player—who still holds the record today",
    answer: "Klay Thompson",
    options: [
      "Kevin Love",
      "Devin Booker",
      "Klay Thompson",
      "James Harden"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 2,
    question: "The first NBA game was played between the New York Knicks and the Toronto Huskies in what year?",
    answer: "1946",
    options: [
      "1946",
      "1947",
      "1960",
      "1990"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: "The National Basketball Association was originally called what?",
    answer: "The Basketball Association of America",
    options: [
      "The National NBA",
      "The National Basketball League",
      "The National Basketball Association",
      "The Basketball Association of America"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Held in Boston Madison Square Garden Club, the first NBA All-Star game took place in what year?",
    answer: "1951",
    options: [
      "1960",
      "1950",
      "1951",
      "1975"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 5,
    question: "Which NBA team has made the most appearances in the finals?",
    answer: "Los Angeles Lakers",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Detroit Pistons"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 6,
    question: "The Lakers are tied with what other NBA team with 17 Championships?",
    answer: "Boston Celtics",
    options: [
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "New York Knicks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 7,
    question: "In 1995, this 6-seed was the lowest-seeded team in NBA history to win a Championship",
    answer: "Houston Rockets",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Houston Rockets"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "The first and only team based outside the United States to win an NBA title or reach the NBA Finals",
    answer: "Blast",
    options: [
      "Milwaukee Bucks",
      "Denver Nuggets",
      "Toronto Raptors",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Which player has the most career blocks in the Finals?",
    answer: "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
    options: [
      "Shaquille O'Neal",
      "Tim Duncan",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Hakeem Olajuwon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "This player has the most turnovers in the Finals",
    answer: "LeBron James",
    options: [
      "LeBron James",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Kobe Bryant",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 11,
    question: "In one series, who had the most steals?",
    answer: "Isaiah Thomas",
    options: [
      "Chris Paul",
      "Alvin Robertson",
      "Isaiah Thomas",
      "Michael Ray Richardson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 12,
    question: "This player had the most 3-point field goals, during one series of the Finals",
    answer: "Steph Curry",
    options: [
      "Klay Thompson",
      "Steph Curry",
      "LeBron James",
      "James Harden"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 13,
    question: "Who is the player that led in overall career point tally in the Finals?",
    answer: "Jerry West",
    options: [
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "LeBron James",
      "Jerry West"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 14,
    question: "What NBA team has made the most franchise Final appearances without winning a title?",
    answer: "Phoenix Suns",
    options: [
      "Miami Heat",
      "Houston Rockets",
      "Phoenix Suns",
      "Indiana Pacers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 15,
    question: "Which player managed to win the NBA Finals MVP Award, even though they were on the losing team?",
    answer: "Jerry West",
    options: [
      "Kevin Durant",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Jerry West"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 16,
    question: "Which was the first team to make it to the NBA finals ten years running?",
    answer: "Boston Celtics",
    options: [
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Washington Wizards"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 17,
    question: "A legendary player, he had the most NBA Finals appearances",
    answer: "Bill Russell",
    options: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Michael Jordan",
      "Bill Russell",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 18,
    question: "The last team to sweep their opponent in a Final",
    answer: "Golden State Warriors",
    options: [
      "Detroit Pistons",
      "Cleveland Cavaliers",
      "Golden State Warriors",
      "San Antonio Spurs"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 19,
    question: "This team has the best winning percentage in the Finals",
    answer: "Chicago Bulls",
    options: [
      "Miami Heat",
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Boston Celtics",
      "Chicago Bulls"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 20,
    question: "Which team won the first NBA Championship?",
    answer: "Philadelphia Warriors",
    options: [
      "Anderson Packers",
      "Philadelphia Warriors",
      "Indianapolis Jets",
      "Waterloo Hawks"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 21,
    question: "The first team to hire a woman on their coaching staff?",
    answer: "San Antonio Spurs",
    options: [
      "Dallas Mavericks",
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "Atlanta Hawks",
      "San Antonio Spurs"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 22,
    question: "In 2004 an altercation occurred mid-game between two teams in an incident that became known as ‘Malice at the Palace’. Which two teams were involved?",
    answer: "Indiana Pacers & Detroit Pistons",
    options: [
      "Indiana Pacers & Detroit Pistons",
      "New York Knicks & Boston Celtics",
      "Los Angeles Lakers & Miami Heat",
      "Golden State Warriors & Phoenix Suns"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 23,
    question: "How many championships did the Boston Celtics win from 1957 to 1969?",
    answer: "11",
    options: [
      "10",
      "13",
      "11",
      "9"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 24,
    question: "This Miami team joined the NBA in 1988",
    answer: "Miami Heat",
    options: [
      "Orlando Magic",
      "Miami Heat",
      "Indiana Pacers",
      "Memphia Grizzlies"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 25,
    question: "Which team did Larry Bird coach during the 1997-98 season?",
    answer: "Indian Pacers",
    options: [
      "Oklohoma City Thunder",
      "Brooklyn Nets",
      "New York Knicks",
      "Indian Pacers"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 26,
    question: "Who was the shortest player to ever win the Slam Dunk contest?",
    answer: "Spud Webb",
    options: [
      "Earl Boykins",
      "Muggsy Bogues",
      "Spud Webb",
      "Keith Jennings"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 27,
    question: "Which player attempted a record number of free throws (39) in an NBA post-season game?",
    answer: "Shaquille O’Neal",
    options: [
      "Bob Cousy",
      "Shaquille O’Neal",
      "DeAndre Jordan",
      "Michael Jordan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 28,
    question: "Who was the first player to win the MVP in consecutive seasons?",
    answer: "Bill Russell",
    options: [
      "Bill Russell",
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Kareem Abdul-Jabbar",
      "Michael Jordan"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 29,
    question: "Who was the first player in the NBA to hit an elusive triple-double season?",
    answer: "Oscar Robertson",
    options: [
      "Nikola Jokic",
      "Russell Westbrook",
      "LeBron James",
      "Oscar Robertson"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 30,
    question: "The first NBA athlete to win both the MVP and Rookie of the Year titles in the same season?",
    answer: "Wilt Chamberlain",
    options: [
      "Wilt Chamberlain",
      "Derrick Rose",
      "Magic Johnson",
      "Stephen Curry"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 31,
    question: "Who owns the Los Angeles Lakers?",
    answer: "Jeanie Buss",
    options: [
      "Joe Lacob",
      "Tilman Fertitta",
      "Jeanie Buss",
      "Herbert Simon"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 32,
    question: "How many personal fouls does it take to get ejected from an NBA basketball game?",
    answer: "6",
    options: [
      "5",
      "6",
      "3",
      "1"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 33,
    question: "When was the shot clock introduced into NBA regulation?",
    answer: "1955",
    options: [
      "1990",
      "1950",
      "1962",
      "1955"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 34,
    question: "How tall is the hoop in the NBA?",
    answer: "10 feet",
    options: [
      "9 feet",
      "12 feet",
      "10 feet",
      "13 feet"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 35,
    question: "When a team is granted a time-out, play will resume only when...",
    answer: "The time-out clock has expired",
    options: [
      "The teams make free throws",
      "The coaches fight",
      "The game is over",
      "The time-out clock has expired"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 36,
    question: "Who invented the sport of basketball?",
    answer: "James Naismith",
    options: [
      "James Naismith",
      "Jerry West",
      "Walter Meanwell",
      "Serge Ibaka"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 37,
    question: "When was basketball first introduced into the Olympics?",
    answer: "1936",
    options: [
      "1940",
      "1936",
      "1950",
      "1935"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 38,
    question: "How many teams play in the NBA?",
    answer: "30",
    options: [
      "30", 
      "27",
      "20",
      "34"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 39,
    question: "Who was the 2001 number 1 overall pick in the draft?",
    answer: "Kwame Brown",
    options: [
      "Tyson Chandler", 
      "Pau Gasol",
      "Joe Johnson",
      "Kwame Brown"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 40,
    question: "Who won the NBA dunk contest in 2016",
    answer: "Zach Lavine",
    options: [
      "Aaron Gordon", 
      "Zach Lavine",
      "Victor Oladipo",
      "Will Barton"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 41,
    question: "Magic Johnson was inducted into the NBA Hall of Fame in what year?",
    answer: "2002",
    options: [
      "1999", 
      "2000",
      "2001",
      "2002"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 42,
    question: "How many NBA officials are in a game? ",
    answer: "3",
    options: [
      "3", 
      "2",
      "4",
      "5"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 43,
    question: "Which NBA team won eight consecutive championships from 1959 to 1966?",
    answer: "Boston Celtics",
    options: [
      "Boston Celtics", 
      "Los Angeles Lakers",
      "Chicago Bulls",
      "Miami Heat"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 44,
    question: "What is the name of the magical girl protagonist in the anime series 'Sailor Moon'?",
    answer: "Usagi Tsukino",
    options: [
      "Rei Hino", 
      "Lilica Hubert",
      "Usagi Tsukino",
      "Hotaru Tomoe"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 45,
    question: "In the anime series 'Bleach,' what is the name of the main character who becomes a Soul Reaper?",
    answer: "Ichigo Kurosaki",
    options: [
      "Renji Abarai", 
      "Rukia Kuchiki",
      "Karin Kurosaki",
      "Ichigo Kurosaki"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 46,
    question: "Which anime series features a group of high school students forming a music band called 'Hokago Tea Time'?",
    answer: "K-On!",
    options: [
      "Clannad", 
      "Tamako Market",
      "K-On!",
      "Blue Period"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 47,
    question: "What is the name of the navigator and thief who joins Luffy on his journey in the 'One Piece' manga series?",
    answer: "Nami",
    options: [
      "Zoro", 
      "Nami",
      "Robin",
      "Chopper"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 48,
    question: "In what year was the 'Slam Dunk' manga first published?",
    answer: "1990",
    options: [
      "1992", 
      "1991",
      "1989",
      "1990"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 49,
    question: "Who is Naruto's teacher in the 'Naruto' manga series?",
    answer: "Iruka",
    options: [
      "Hiruzen", 
      "Asuma",
      "Iruka",
      "Tsunade"
    ]
  },
  {
    numb: 50,
    question: "At the conclusion of the 'Naruto' manga series, who does Naruto marry?",
    answer: "Hinata",
    options: [
      "Hinata", 
      "Sakura",
      "Ino",
      "Tenten"
    ]
  },
    
];

